A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14 FA286
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
1925-1951
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA286
51.92 Cubic Feet 118 boxes
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement note
This series is arranged in 4 subseries:
Subseries 1 - Appeals
Subseries 2 - General Division Files
Subseries 3 - Project Files
Subseries 4 - Rochester Regional Plan
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Scope and Contents note
Prior to 1925 the Commonwealth Fund granted only limited monies for the building or enlargement of hospitals, i.e., to Yale University for improvements to the New Haven Hospital, to the Grenfell Association for small hospitals in Newfoundland, to the Presbyterian Board of Missions for a hospital at Point Barrow, Alaska, and to Memorial Hospital in New York City to aid in the construction of a new building. The Fund's experiences with the Child Health Demonstrations included more than just child health services and brought the realization of the need for improved medical and surgical facilities in rural America. In June 1925 Henry C. Wright, hospital consultant, studied the possibilities of improving rural hospital services. Wright's study led to the establishment of the Division of Rural Hospitals and the appointment, in March 1926, of a director, Henry J. Southmayd, who served in that capacity throughout the division's existence.
Selection of sites was determined by the capacity and willingness of rural communities to help themselves. In districts lacking both towns of over 12,000 and hospitals, the Fund supplied the greater part, but not all, of the building costs, with the communities providing the remainder and then maintaining the institutions. The hospitals were viewed as health centers that also provided professional education, thereby developing public health and hospital service side by side. Six small hospitals were established throughout the United States between 1926 and 1930, but worsening financial conditions momentarily discouraged further construction. For the next five years the program emphasized the strengthening of hospital administration and service. Outpatient care was developed, staff libraries and accounting procedures were improved and fixed or inclusive rate schedules were introduced. The financial picture had improved considerably by 1934 and the building program was begun again, with an additional ten hospitals being constructed. With the passage of the Hospital Survey and Construction (Hill-Burton) Act in 1946, federal funds were now available for hospital construction costs, and as an outgrowth, the Fund decided to terminate its building program in 1946.
The Fund's activities in rural hospitals clarified the difficulties and limitations faced by small hospitals, and in 1943 the Fund concluded that some of these problems might be overcome by broadening the concept of community. Consequently, the Fund offered a plan for regional development utilizing the formation of closer ties among the hospitals in small cities and those in large urban centers. The goal was to determine how voluntary action through a regional organization would benefit the quality of the hospital service rendered. The Rochester, New York, area was chosen for this experiment. Three fields of action were introduced: 1) the joint planning of hospital building and expansion, 2) the mutual operation of services that could be offered more efficiently by a group, and 3) the pooling of clinical administrative and technical skills. In 1953 the Fund commissioned the Institute of Administrative Medicine, Columbia University, to survey the regional plan. The result of this study, "The Rochester Regional Hospital Council," by Leonard S. Rosenfeld and Henry B. Makover, was published by Harvard University Press in 1956.
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Law; Legal issues; Legal research; Medical education; Child psychology; Child welfare; Education, Rural; Hygiene; Medical research; Medicine, Rural; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Mental health; New York (State); Public health; Child mental health; New York (N.Y.); War relief; Public welfare; United States; Yale University; Phillips Exeter Academy; Harkness, Mary Emma Stillman; Social Science Research Council; Columbia University; Harkness, Edward Stephen; Harkness, Charles W.; Harvard University; Harkness, Anna M. Richardson
- Appeals, 1
  - Chronological List of Appeals (#1 to #926), 1925-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General Files, 1926-1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General Files, 1926-1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General Files, 1926-1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - State File - Alaska, Petersburg (Correspondence), September 16-21, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - State File - Arkansas, Helena (Correspondence), 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - State File - Arkansas, Paragould (Correspondence), 1938-1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - State File - Arkansas, Paragould (Correspondence), 1938-1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - State File - Arkansas, West Memphis (Correspondence), August 21-26, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - State File, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Scope and Contents note
    British Columbia, Vancouver (Correspondence) - August 19-21, 1946 California, Palm Springs (Correspondence) - December 4, 1937-January 23, 1947
  - State File - Florida, Bradenton (Correspondence), 1937-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - State File - Florida, Bradenton (Correspondence), 1937-1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - State File - Florida, Fort Myers (Correspondence), 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - State File - Florida, Lake City (Correspondence), 1931-1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - State File - Florida, Marianna (Annual Reports), 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - State File - Florida, Marianna (Chamber of Commerce Publications), 1937 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - State File - Florida, Marianna (Correspondence), 1935-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - State File - Florida, Marianna (Correspondence), 1935-1946 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - State File - Florida, Marianna (Statistics), 1930-1936 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - State File - Georgia, Louisville (Correspondence), 1925-1933 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - State File - Hawaii, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Kaunakakai, Molokai (Correspondence) - August 12-15, 1949 Paia, Maui (Correspondence) - May 21-23, 1941
  - State File - Illinois, Mendota (Correspondence), 1944-1949 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - State File - Illinois, Mt. Carmel (Correspondence), 1926-1927; 1947 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - State File - Kentucky, Hopkinsville (Correspondence), December 5-15, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - State File - Kentucky, Somerset (Correspondence), 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - State File - Michigan, Romeo (Correspondence), March 18-27, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - State File - Mississippi, Clarksdale (Correspondence), 1940-1949 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - State File - Mississippi, Greenwood (Correspondence), 1937-1945 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - State File - Mississippi, Gulfport (Correspondence), 1935-1939 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - State File - Mississippi, Laurel (Correspondence), 1926-1945 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - State File - Mississippi, Laurel (Correspondence), 1926-1945 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - State File - Mississippi, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Mound Bayou (Correspondence) - April 20-24, 1950 West Point (Correspondence) - February 4, 1947-March 21, 1951
  - State File - Missouri, Kennett (Correspondence), 1926-1939 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - State File - New Hampshire, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Hanover (Correspondence) - September 14, 1936-January 16, 1940 Peterborough (Correspondence) - October 16, 1936-October 8, 1946
  - State File - New Hampshire, Rochester (Correspondence), 1930-1948 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - State File - New Mexico, Santa Fe (Correspondence), 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - State File - New York, Bay Shore (Correspondence), 1936-1947 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - State File - New York, Canton (Correspondence), 1946-1950 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - State File - North Carolina, Asheboro (Correspondence), 1945-1947 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - State File - Ohio, Oberlin College (Correspondence), 1947-1951 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - State File - Oklahoma, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Blackwell (Correspondence) - June 22, 1937-October 21, 1939 McAlester (Correspondence) - August 26, 1949-September 1, 1949
  - State File - Oregon, Newburg (Correspondence), March 10-15, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - State File - South Carolina, Kingstree (Correspondence), 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - State File - South Dakota, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 44)
    Chamberlain (Correspondence) - January 24, 1940-February 26, 1947 Huron (Correspondence) - September 22, 1926-January 18, 1944
  - State File - Tennessee, Crossville (Correspondence), June-July, 1928; 1941-1946 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - State File - Tennessee, Johnson City (Correspondence), 1932-1947 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - State File - Tennessee, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 47)
    Madison College (Correspondence) - November 24, 1945-December 9, 1945 Sevierville (Correspondence) - October 16, 1935-October 8, 1940
  - State File - Tennessee, Trenton (Correspondence), 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - State File - Tennessee, Trenton (Correspondence), 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - State File - Tennessee, Union City (Correspondence), 1926-1944 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - State File - Tennessee, Union City (Correspondence), 1926-1944 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - State File - Tennessee, San Saba (Correspondence), 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - State File - Virginia, Waynesboro (Correspondence), 1946-1950 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - State File - Wyoming, Cody (Correspondence), 1936-1938 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - State File - Wyoming, Cody (Correspondence), 1936-1938 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - State File - Wyoming, Cody (Correspondence), 1936-1938 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- General Division Files, 2
  - Accounting Manual, 1932; 1932; 1934; 1938; 1945 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Accounting Manual, 1932; 1932; 1934; 1938; 1945 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Accounting Manual, 1932; 1932; 1934; 1938; 1945 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Accounting Manual, 1932; 1932; 1934; 1938; 1945 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Accounting Manual, 1932; 1932; 1934; 1938; 1945 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Agreement Forms and Contracts, 1925-1933; 1938-1943 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Agreement Forms and Contracts, 1925-1933; 1938-1943 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Agreement Forms and Contracts, 1925-1933; 1938-1943 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Agreement Forms and Contracts, 1925-1933; 1938-1943 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Annual Reports, 1926-1949 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Appraisals of Medical Practices - Memoranda and Reports, 1931-1948 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Appraisals of Medical Practices - Memoranda and Reports, 1931-1948 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Appraisals of Medical Practices - Statistics, 1931-1937 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1925-1937 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Architects' Correspondence and Reports - Index, 1925-1952 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Articles by Rural Hospital Division Staff, 1938-1940; 1943-1949 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Articles by Rural Hospital Division Staff, 1938-1940; 1943-1949 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Articles on Rural Hospitals, 1928-1934 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Auditors' Correspondence and Reports, 1930-1950 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Auditors' Correspondence and Reports, 1930-1950 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Auditors' Correspondence and Reports, 1930-1950 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Auditors' Correspondence and Reports, 1930-1950 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Auditors' Correspondence and Reports, 1930-1950 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Budget Material, 1933-1946 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Budget Material, 1933-1946 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Budget Material, 1933-1946 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Budget Material, 1933-1946 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Budget Material, 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Budget Material, 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Cancer Program - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Cancer Program - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Cancer Program - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Cancer Program - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Candidates for Employment - Executive (B-D) (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Candidates for Employment - Executive (E) (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Candidates for Employment - Executive (H-L) (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Candidates for Employment - Executive (M) (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Candidates for Employment - Executive (P-Z) (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Candidates for Employment - Miscellaneous (A-W) (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Candidates for Employment - Pathologist (D-S) (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Candidates for Employment - Resident Physician - Applications (D-V) (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Candidates for Employment - Resident Physician - Correspondence and Memoranda (B-Y) (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Candidates for Employment - Roentgenologist (A-O) (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Candidates for Employment - Technicians (A-E) (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Candidates for Employment - Technicians (F-K) (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Candidates for Employment - Technicians (L-R) (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Candidates for Employment - Technicians (S-W) (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Hospitals (Ada, Oklahoma) (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Hospitals (Beloit, Kansas; Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Hospitals (Farmington, Maine; Farmville, Virginia; Glasgow, Kentucky) (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Hospitals (Kingsport, Tennessee; Lancaster, South Carolina) (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Hospitals (Mt. Pleasant, Michigan; Murfreesboro, Tennessee; Pittsfield, Illinois; Provo, Utah) (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Hospitals (Sikeston, Missouri; Tupelo, Mississippi; Wauseon, Ohio) (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Medical Staff (Ada, Oklahoma; Beloit, Kansas; Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Medical Staff (Farmington, Maine; Farmville, Virginia) (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Medical Staff (Glasgow, Kentucky; Kingsport, Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Medical Staff (Lancaster, South Carolina; Mt. Pleasant, Michigan; Murfreesboro, Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Medical Staff (Provo, Utah) (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Medical Staff (Tupelo, Mississippi; Wauseon, Ohio) (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 163)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 164)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 167)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 171)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 172)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 174)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 175)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 176)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 177)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 178)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 179)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 180)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 181)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 182)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 183)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 184)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 185)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 186)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 187)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 190)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 191)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 194)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 195)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 196)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 197)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 198)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 199)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 200)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 14, Folder 201)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 204)